acprail.com 2019-03-17

# Privacy Policy

## Who are we?

ACP Marketing is a privately-owned marketing and distribution company specializing in international rail sales. Our address is Room F2. 1 231, Vauxhall Bridge Road, London, SW1V 1AD, United Kingdom. ACP Marketing comprises ACP Rail International, Accesrail, ACP Railnet and ACP Secrets. 

## How do we collect information from you?

We collect information from you when you use our websites, contact our call center, register to our newsletters, fill out an order or enter a sweepstakes.

## What type of information is collected from you?

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (name and shipping address, etc) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date.) 

## How is your information used?

This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Name and Contact Details**

Get in touch with you

In case there is a problem.

Deliver your purchases to you

We need your contact information to be able to send you your tickets. 

Fraud prevention and detection

To prevent and detect fraud against you or ACP Marketing. 

Sending you our newsletter

In order to inform you about our latest sales, sweepstakes and new products. We only send you this with your permission

**Date of Birth**

Fraud prevention and detection

To prevent and detect fraud against you or ACP Marketing. 

**Your payment information**

Take payment and give refunds

Your payment information is used to bill you for our products and services.

Fraud prevention and detection

To prevent and detect fraud against you or ACP Marketing. 

**Purchase history**

Your shopping cart

To keep track of your shopping cart. If you can’t add things to the basket, you can’t buy it.

Customer service and support as well as handle returns.

With this information, we can help you as much as we can and ensure you the best shopping experience. 

**Information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website and app**

Improve our website and set your language, country and currency for you. 

To give you the best shopping experience by making sure the products that are visible are available in your market as well as making sure that the prices are accurate.

Protect our website.

To prevent and detect fraud against you or ACP Marketing. 

You don’t have to give us your personal information. However, in order to buy from our website as well as use it, you will need to provide us with this information. If you don’t want to, that’s okay!

However, if you do share with us your personal information, we anonymize it. This information is used for data analysis and to improve our website.

## Who has access to your information?

The information you provide will not be shared to third parties. We also do not sell your information for marketing purposes.

However, we do share your information with Third Party Service Providers that work on our behalf. When we do, we only disclose the information that is absolutely necessary for the purpose of completing their tasks. Here are the categories of providers: 

  * Payment service providers (in order to process your payment)
  * Professional service providers (This includes marketing and advertising agencies)
  * Analytics (The information provided is anonymous so they cannot identify you)

## Your choices/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [info@acprail.com](mailto:info@acprail.com).

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

## How you can access and update your information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This may be done by emailing us at [info@acprail.com](mailto:info@acprail.com).

## Keeping your information

Since we sell products on behalf of our partners (train operators), we are required to hold on to your personal information for a minimum of 7 years for legal and audit purposes. This information never includes your payment information. Your payment information is only used during billing purposes. Since we use a payment service provider (World Pay), we never have access to that information. 

## Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer.) While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [webmaster@ACPRail.com](mailto:webmaster@ACPRail.com).

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Our site uses different types of cookies. 

  1. Site functionality: These cookies allow you to use our website like adding products to your cart as well as to keep track of your shopping cart when navigating to different pages of our website.
  2. Site analytics: These cookies provide us with information on how customers use your website in order to optimize the way customers use our website and their shopping experience.
  3. Customer preference: These cookies remember your location as well as currency so when you come back to our website it makes the whole shopping experience more seamless. 
  4. Targeting or Advertising: These cookies are used during our marketing campaigns to make sure that our targeted ads are relevant to you.

In order to ensure the functionality of our website, cookies are essential. If a user rejects the cookie, they will not be able to take advantage of our websites since cookies are essential in retrieving products and prices. However, you have the right to [refuse cookies](https://www.acprail.com/clearcookies.php) at any point in time. 

## Links to other websites

Our website has links to other organizations. You should be aware that: 

  * If you access another site through a link we provide, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site.
  * Reference in this referred website to commercial products, services, manufacturers, or companies does not constitute an endorsement by ACP Marketing.
  * ACP Marketing is not responsible for the contents to any linked sites.

## Marketing messages

If we received your permission, we will send you marketing messages by email to keep you aware of the latest news. This includes our promotions, sweepstakes and our newest products.

**How to stop receiving our marketing messages**  
You can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time. You can do this by simply clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in our emails. You can also do this by contacting our Customer service team at [info@acprail.com](mailto:info@acprail.com)

## Seeing adverts for ACPRail.com online

Like many other websites, we use remarketing tools to target ACP Rail banner and ads to you when you are on other websites. 

The banners and ads you see are based on information we hold about you. This information can include cookies or ACP Rail banners or ads you have previously clicked on.

## Transferring your information outside of Europe

We have fulfilment centers in Canada, China, Australia and the United Kingdom. However, all orders from the EU are processed and fulfilled in London, UK.

## 16 or Under

ACP Marketing is concerned to protect the privacy of minors. If you are 16 or under please get parental approval before you provide us with personal information.

## Notification of Changes

Any material changes in the way ACP Marketing uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Statement or our privacy practices to [webmaster@ACPRail.com](mailto:webmaster@ACPRail.com).

Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. ACP Marketing will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt
